Young man, why did
n't you delete it?  Haven't you deleted chat roulette?
Well, for now, yes.  Imagine,
no.
Listen, no one answered you.  I said
that I had a desire to delete chat
roulette for one reason or another.  The fact
that I didn't do this,
you said it all, I'm deleting it tomorrow.  That's how
you talk.   Am
I giving you some kind of word there or what did
you say?  You said, I'm answering right now,
tomorrow I'm removing this worm.   I'll
sit out today.  You said so, we have
everything written down.
Yeah, damn
, I said I'll answer.
Yes, it was.  I answer the word.  People,
give me a plus.  He replied that he would sit out the
day, but tomorrow he would no longer be there.  Yes,
they will give you pluses there now.   They'll
even add upvotes.  If you gave a
Russian there, even they would
n't see this video.
Listen, were you the one trading at Wilbury or your
wife?
No, I've never done that.
Understood.  So, did they really burn those
Walberries that hard?
Well, of course, it's
terrible.  Do you know anyone
who, in short, has
six logistics hubs, the
biggest ones, yes, there
m
Yes, yes, yes.  Six big ones, the biggest
six logistics centers, yes, they
went boom.   Do
you know anyone who
traded on Viber and went bankrupt because of
it?
Well, no, listen, I didn’t have such acquaintances
, because, firstly, I
always order
all my orders from Ozon only.  Well,
by the way, my wife even orders from Walbere.  Well,
apparently, the distribution to Te
Regino is going on.  This does not apply to Moscow.
Yes, a lot of things burned down, especially a
lot of businesses burned down in Moscow, yes.  I
think that the people there Well, this is Kim, she
Well, this is Kim, she always bent over
her individual entrepreneurs,
sellers, yes,
she always had exorbitant conditions there even before
their goods were burned.  I think that it would be
even better for them if there was less, it would be better
for Russia.  Yes, they lost
money, but maybe there will be some
competition within
Russia, like Ozon.  Listen,
maybe it's Sberbank and the
Russian government, so they can
sell through Sber?  In short, do
you think they won't hit me further with Azon?
Well, I don't... Well, no, most likely, hardly.
Why?
Azon
does not have its own large logistics
centers.  That is, Ozone works a little differently
.
Well, he'll hit the Ozone.  Okay, I'll
go to Sadovod.
Receiving.  So, Sadovod was already on fire, when this is what caused
the fire there, by the way, Sadovod is also a
new topic for us.  I'll reveal
which one now,
otherwise, suddenly, "
Listen, wait, how is Ozon different from Wiberies
?"  It turns out that Viber Berry
stores sellers' goods in its
warehouses, and Ozon simply accepts orders
and sellers ship them directly.  Yes,
look, Valberis, as I understand it, is the
first player to enter the
market, yes, in Russia, specifically with
online stores and so on.
That is, she built a bunch of warehouses, huge
warehouses, yes, a bunch of logistics
there and so on.  Ozon is the player
that entered the market second or third
, that is, essentially, they are most likely
renting some premises from
someone.  there are no actual
huge centers built there.
Well, I think so.  I may be
wrong,
but for some reason,
I’ve always used Ozone there, I still
use it.  Well, I don't know.
Understood.  What, for example, that you
don’t order on Viber?
Yes, I don't know.  Well, you know,
somehow it worked out for me.  Well, I started with Ozono.
I'm a boy, I don't really look for where it's
cheaper, where something is.  I
installed UZON there and ordered it.  But you know what
I think?  This is simply a future fix.
Now we are telling you that you are telling us so that we can come to
an agreement later, so as to, roughly speaking, not
burn down certain warehouses.
Here is the first one, all of this, that is,
your mail there and so on.  In response, they showed:
"Listen, we can do it too. You should
think about it so that we can come to an
agreement later. That's all.
So. And listen, don't you think that
Russia can no longer
counter anything except nuclear weapons, right, uh, against
Ukrainian shelling on its
territory?
Honestly, I don't want that. God forbid that
happens. I don't want it to get to that
point where Russia has nothing, well,
to counter, except for me, there's
nothing left to counter.
Yeah, well, I, well, listen, I live in Moscow
and I move around Moscow a lot, yeah,
I just had
a couple of moments, damn, well, I don't know
if I can say that, no, but in a very,
okay, let's say, messed up, in
very unexpected places
such complexes appear inside the city, when you... I'm
driving a car, first there's a traffic police car
, a traffic police car, then a military
inspection car and there
I think, wow, we definitely won't...
We expected it. If before the Kremlin just had
three soldiers standing there, yeah, anti-aircraft guns,
in short, now, well, it's like, well,
Russia is learning, that is,
learning, yeah.
Me, me
, well, and Ukraine isn't lagging behind in its studies,
right?
Well, Ukraine,
yeah, Ukraine too, of course, well,
damn, Ukraine plus all of Europe plus, yeah, we
won't even take all of Europe, yeah, I'll
most likely take American
companies. I mean, what has America always
been famous for, yeah? It's a huge
arms lobby,
it's a multi-billion dollar
lobby, yeah. Yeah,
even leaving aside the war, they simply
armed their own country within their own country,
so they
armed it, yeah.
I mean, why is it impossible to go to America? You
go to America, it's
impossible.
From every second house there's this
machine gun, yeah, it'll appear there, because
everyone is armed,
so there's this huge American lobby,
which,
yeah, arms, yeah. Well, what's so
surprising about that?
Got it.
What do you think, Trump, right,
told you that they gave you the Petrit blueprints
? Is that some kind of advantage or is this
some kind of first?
No, not the Petrit blueprints. As I understand it,
they're creating a franchise for
Patriot production outside of US capacities. That
is, in Europe, here in Ukraine or Poland,
will they produce, as I understand it?
Well, hardly in Ukraine. Well, I most likely
think they gave these blueprints to
Ukraine. It's impossible to build such a plant inside Ukraine
.
No, look, look again. No, don't
look. Naturally, no one is going to give out any blueprints,
right? Uh, the facilities are being built
, yes, production facilities, yes,
engineers are working there, like chief engineers of
certain, well, American companies,
yes, they have this documentation, yes, it
will simply be produced under a franchise
and, well
, it's just that here, you know, in our country
they laugh about it there, yes, everyone, well, I
see there on various channels, they are included in my
recommendations. Here in the country there is
confusion about the fact that  Ahaha, what kind of
plant would they build in Ukraine? They'd immediately
demolish it because, well, it would have to be a
certain large plant and so
on. Well, let's be honest, but no one would
build such a plant in Ukraine.
They'd build it in Europe.
Of course. In Europe, yes. And they'd say
it's in Ukraine,
in Europe, just like most
production facilities are in Europe now, and they'd simply
supply Ukraine with it. This is something
worth thinking about. That's all.
Yes. And just like they supply drones and
missiles there, right? And you poor things are suffering
now.
Poor things,
right?
Well, I think Russia is definitely not a
poor thing.
Why?
Let there be sanctions, let me be
10 years old there today, well, not 10, please, 6
years ago I could buy a BMW for 2 million,
now I have to pay 10, let
everything have gone up in price there and so on and so forth
. Even if
I understand that I'm
somehow limiting myself,  some of these and
so on, but
I don't see, I don't look at my drunken
president, like that Yeltsin, who
danced there in all the countries of America
and so on, when there was
complete devastation in the country.
Well, I think that we will still come to something with
ours. It's, you know, like
at school, in short, you either sit there your whole life
in an average party, in short, it's like
you're there, it's like you're not there, and
so on. Or you go and fight,
in short, one day, the second day, the third
day, the fourth day. Yes, I changed five schools
. I fought in every school.
You could receive, you could give these, but
sooner or later you came to the
status that they took you into account.
That's all.
Got it. Isn't that
right?
Not like that.
Not like that. And how?
No, well, of course, you can, like America,
sit there your whole life on your own continent,
trade in weapons, rise thanks to
World War II. Why did America
become rich at all?  Well, they traded in the
second one,
right? They did, yes. They traded left and right
and simply made huge amounts of money
. Now they're doing the
same.
Yes. And they're not letting Russia trade,
you understand?
I understand.
That is, Russia was thrown out of trade. This is
because there were certain events
inside Russia that led to this.
Well, now the SVO, yes, has led to
Russia being thrown out of these trade
chains. Just
as they throw it out, so they bring it back. There's a
statement from that same Macron that we
need to listen to Russia [snorts] and
finally start some kind of relationship.
No, that didn't happen.
When did they add more sanctions after that
? Europe always says that
we need to start the same way Trump and Rubio are
feeding that Lavrov the spirit of Anchorage,
that yes, we need to reboot, we need to, we need to, we need to
, yes. Oops.
Well, looking at today, yes, what's
happening, I think,
listen, I can't make a 100%
decision. Time will tell.  On the one
hand, I support all of this, on the other
hand, I think it's savagery. I
mean, well, today it's... So
you support savagery?
To some extent? Yes. To some
extent, I have, I have, honestly, I have a
contradiction in my soul, that's why I
go to chat roulette. Listen, if I
were 100% sure of something, I
would never have come here. I would...
Listen, am I right, look, am I right in
understanding that you understand that every
day of this war throws
your country's economy and demography back, yes, to the
Middle Ages.
Well, not to the Middle Ages, come on.
Well, figuratively speaking,
no need. Figuratively speaking, to me. I looked,
you know, why am I now a little, I
'll be more careful how I communicate with you. I
watched your dialogue with this Nopsel,
with this young man, in short, the bespectacled guy,
who is a historian, some kind of blogger.
Obon as much as he could, in short, he just
pissed on me as much as he could. Well, that's why he  That he's
small, he's young, in short. Well, he's a
little there,
yeah, where he says he's in his
20s, in short, almost thirty.
Good for him. Listen, I often argued with him too
, quarreled. I often, well,
this Nopsel, he, in short,
tried to, in short, these
books about history and so on, but
when he's just mocked, he doesn't
get it, he's all, he gets lost, in short,
he's just tactless
about history, in short, you know, well, damn,
that's why I understand that you're very good at it
and so on. Of all my
bloggers, there's only one blogger in
Russia whom I have a very
good attitude towards. This is a voluntary collective farm business. A
real gem. He almost never communicates with bloggers, with
yours.
They're all afraid of us. They're afraid. Your
bloggers.
He has different content. He doesn't have
this, you know, talking about history with
someone there, according to documents, purely
on  It's a joke, it's just a joke. Well, he's such a
normal guy, he's very well
-regarded and he helps the front a lot
. Okay, we're not talking about that.
Yes, I understand that today, and
I understand that, God forbid, well, of course,
it's unlikely there will be a mobilization in the fall,
most likely, it's unlikely. I
think it will be right after the elections in the fall.
Yes.
Look, if the
UD strikes in 2022, it hits very hard,
mm, you see, there's the history of Russia, right?
There's the history of Russia, where the people
suffer for a very long time, 100-200 years,
then the country is simply drowning in blood.
We suffer a revolution for 100-200 years, and then the
country is covered in blood again, in short, revolution. And I
think that smart people who hold
certain positions, they
understand that at some point people
may snap. Now, these same
UD strikes against Wildberries, against Moscow, I
think that they are going
against Ukraine,  Because those people who were
sitting in Moscow, they didn't know what
war was. It's there, it's somewhere far away,
somewhere. Well,
that's it. So what will happen now?
What now? Well, some brainwashed
foreigner,
some brainwashed son-in-law, who,
every day, oh-oh-oh-oh, they
hit him, he doesn't have gasoline,
he doesn't have that, he'll just go and sign a
contract. That's all.
Look, uh, it's very simple, yes, we see
the situation in the Belgorod, Kursk, and
Bryansk regions. There, for how many
years now, yes, that's it, yes. And for some reason,
people haven't rushed from there en masse to sign
the contract, they've rushed to get out of those regions
, but they haven't signed the contract. That
's why, look, Russian propaganda very often
says: "Look, Ukraine has struck
factories there, these marketplaces, that's it
, now people will go and sign the
contract." No, more than that, look, uh,
in all the videos,  Yes, arrivals,
oil refineries, gas stations
, I didn't hear anyone yelling,
and you, ethics, yeah, they just say, you
know, wow, wow.
We don't have anything like that in Russia, that's
not why we hate, look, so look, the strikes
on the oil refineries in
Vaberis, no one will be sent to the front,
you understand? These people, like, won't go to the
front because something burned down with Varis.
No, I'm not telling you it will be
massive. There's nothing like that here in Russia.
Listen, if a UA car parked
[clears throat]
in front of my entrance now, yes, there, with
Kyiv license plates, they won't eat it tomorrow, they won't smash it tomorrow
, no one will
touch it. No one will touch that car.
No,
listen straight to us, I'm telling you, look, it's the
same with us, if
this car with
Russian license plates parked in front of my entrance  Moskov, yes, no
one will defeat the Russians tomorrow. They
won't defeat them tomorrow.
They will defeat them today.
So today, [laughter]
tomorrow no one will touch them, because there will be nothing to
touch.
Well, tomorrow, in short, they will take them apart for
spare parts and burn them. No, you see, there is
none here. I personally don't. Many people
don't hate the citizens of Ukraine. But there is
simply no such hatred. There is no such
hatred. It's just that there are certain
people, there are Zetniks, yes, who
are called, well, nerds. I also
call them residents of Russia.
Well, they brainwash him. So he
watches TV, he watches TV, he
watches these bloggers, yes, who are aimed at this,
who tell him the same thing every day
, well, he just listened to this, yes,
and tomorrow he wakes up outside the window and
sees this drone.
Horrible. So what?
And he thinks: "That's it, war has come, let's
go." That's a small percentage.
Nobody,  Look again, look again.
No one, because on the contrary, it
sobers up many,
because before they thought it was just that
, somewhere out there. Moreover, look,
if they understand that it's already flying all the way
to Moscow and so on, then
they also understand that drones are flying at them at the front
. So, don't bother with these
daddies. He's
not a military man, he
can never even imagine in his head what
the situation is like at the front.
Listen, that's it. No, look, it
was possible in '22, when there was
the mobilization of '22. They didn't know the
situation at the front. Now, over these
years, every Russian has acquaintances,
acquaintances who have died, and so on. In short,
who's where, that's it, they all know perfectly well
what kind of horror, uh, is going on there. So, don't be so
loud.
Well, in my, yes, circle there and so on, in the
circle of my friends, even that person
who... Well, no, you're just a little bit...  You're
wrong. There's no such person who
came back from the front and said, "
Yeah, we're all gathered there,
friends, no, don't
go there, you have to run through the bushes
, jump and listen, maybe a bird did
n't take off somewhere, or somewhere
there, in short, there and so on."
No one will tell you this,
because the person who came back from the
front all these years, he has a slightly different way of
thinking. And, most likely, if he
came back in one piece, he will go back there.
Horrible.
So, where do you live? In Ukraine
or...
Yes, you ask me every time.
The city of Khmelnitsky, Ukraine.
Khmelnytskyi. That's it.
[clears throat] You
still want me to live in Europe, right?
Why?
Well, I don't know. You're always like, in short,
asking: "So, are you in
Khmelnitsky, Ukraine, or where?"
See top with him watched this video and he told
me you yourself are somewhere there
in France or Germany  you live
because he says, like, but you're not
in Ukraine, okay, not in Ukraine, like, you know, well,
if he believes, in short, he won't tell him so as
not to argue with him, well, okay,
and what is, like, like,
today, this is your job and
propaganda, you're catching bloggers here, yes,
because you're most likely unlikely to be in
this chat,
look, uh, what am I doing here,
first of all, I'm having a lot of fun, yes, I enjoy
this, yes, I, look, let's start with the
fact that, uh, I get moral
satisfaction,
dominance over all these organisms
that go on chat roulette here, yes, and
I am satisfied with myself, I, in short,
boost my ego and so on. Look,
I have this type, yes, I love for people.
That's how I would piss off some of my
relatives, acquaintances, yes, friends, yes.
And this is how I realize it. Before, they would
tell me: "You're annoying, but now you're annoying
Russians and they tell you: "They meet you on the
street, Andrey, you're a good guy, you know? That
is, you have such a minus behind you, which was
in.
Yes, I turned it into a plus."  Yes.  Yes.
Now let's move on.
Next, I help people undergo
free psycho-training.  For example, uh, let
's say, going to a psychologist is very
expensive now, yes, you must admit.  And,
for example, people have anxiety, yes, there are some other things,
for example.  They
come to my stream, yes, and they
relax, their
kundalini rises, their chakras open, you know?
People see how I send someone, how
I drive them there, they mopped up this
shmopsito.  And people get high, you know?  It's like
watching football.  People
release their negative energy,
it is thrown out, and they feel better.   It's
easier, look, they calmly experience
what is happening in Ukraine, the shelling and
so on.  Yes, it is easier for them.  Are you
talking negativity?
No, I'm being negative.  Rus.  And our A-ha chat,
now.  Okay, stop.  chat.  Well, give me a
plus or Father Androni is bringing you
positivity.  Let's see now.
Yes, listen, I don’t look at your chat, and I’m
telling you this as a person who communicates with you
.  That is,
for you it’s negative,
look, that is, you bring
relaxation to people through negativity.  That's what I'm getting at,
right?  Yes.
So it is normal for a person
to relax when he sees.
Well, look, come on, come on.  So, when,
for example, the boxer Usyk, yes, beats up
another boxer, it’s negative, he beats a
person, yes.  But the people who watched it, they were
positive, you know?
No, don't compare.  Listen,
okay.  Okay, look, let's do it this way.  Let's do it this way
.  A burning oil
refinery, an explosion, yes, in Russia it’s
negative, but for people it’s immediately positive,
you know?  Look, we're looking, yes, at the
burning Wildberries, at these women
who are screaming, ah, I lost everything.  And this is
negative.
So, tomorrow after this arrival on
Wildberries, where you are rejoicing, comes
Russia's response, where there is a million.  No, no,
no, no, look.  No, no, look.
I'll explain again, I'll explain.  There are
no responses from Russia.
Yes, it does not exist.
No, look, Russia was shelling us.
So she started shooting at us.  It's not us who are
giving her answers, you understand?  Even though
we, yes, even though we won’t
shell Wildberries or
non-fire factories, Russia
will still bomb us.  She started bombing us
even before we started snapping back.
That is, the intensity has not changed.
The intensity is not from Look,
the intensity of shelling in Russia depends
on the stock of missiles and drones that
Russia has.  The intensity of shelling between Ukraine
and Russia also depends on the
drone stockpile that Ukraine has.
Ukraine now has more drones and
missiles.  Yes, we are striking your
territory.  That's it, there are no answers
at all.  We are hitting you
because we have the means.  You are
hitting us because you had these
means.  That's all.
And what will this lead to?
It will lead to the destruction of the Russian
Federation and its disintegration into an independent
state.
No, stop, it turns out you're contradicting yourself
.  Why did
you, look, 10 minutes ago you
told me that there might come a
critical moment when the
Russian Federation would use
nuclear weapons.
I was just kidding.  What did I say, I
didn’t say that it’s time I said that
you have nothing to be afraid of except nuclear weapons
, you understand?  You're
talking about nuclear weapons there.  That is, you yourself
understand, you weren’t joking, you understand
this, that at some point there won’t be
any nuclear weapons.  Everything has been
clear since 22nd year.  Then there will
be no defeat of Russia, no division of it into
some parts.
Why?  Why?
Well, because there has to come a
moment when, look, when
you have no trump cards, what, yes, what to hit with.  Have you ever
played cards?  I really
love poker, in short.  Yes, this is
my favorite game in
existence.  I've lost my whole life playing poker
.  And when you don’t have anything, yeah,
any trump cards,
Listen, you said a funny phrase: “I’ve
lost my whole life at poker.”
Well, yes, yes, yes, I lost.  I am a player.  I
lost a lot at the casino.   I've
lost my whole life playing poker.
Well, yes, yes.  When casinos closed in Russia
, I started playing in Belarus.   Are
you that dependent?
Well, I wish there was.  Fortunately, I wanted to say.
Luckily, I haven't played for 5 years now.  I
didn't switch to betting there, like many of my
gambling addict friends, but fortunately I had a
family, a wife, who
removed me from this.
Understood?   Wow
.
But I'm a gambler by nature, that is, well, my
character remains the same in any
case.
Look, about the nuclear one.  The point is that no
one will destroy Russia there by
capturing Moscow.  Nobody is going to go to
Moscow with tanks.  Russia.  Look,
how are they destroying Russia?  They are
strangling it economically, uh, they are breaking up, uh,
logistical connectivity, those same
marketplaces, yes, they are breaking up
oil refineries, yes, because of
which the logistics of transportation are also
becoming more complicated.  So, they are creating a
crisis of statehood in Russia, right?  And because
Russia is huge, yes, your
regional connectivity is very, very
important.  And Russia will be brought to the point where there
will be a shortage of goods, there will be problems, there
will be quarrels, there will be conflicts between regions.
Just like in the Soviet Union.
Listen, do you have any shortages of
fuel or goods?
No.
So look, you have such a small
country that is ironing out, like Yes, you
say, since 22 for
4 years they have been hitting
oil refining, power plants, everything, everything,
all the infrastructure.
You don't have this, where did you get the idea that it's
possible for Russia to occupy
Europe? Yes, that's a good question, yes,
because, look, Ukraine's entire rear
is Europe.  Ukraine, if, look,
if it were simply isolated,
yes, if Europe hadn't helped it, it would have
collapsed in the first weeks, yes,
Ukraine, yes, Europe supports us with financial influence
, yes, our social security
is supported and so on, uh, with oil, that is,
gasoline and so on.  It's all from
Europe too, right?  That is, in essence, our rear
is Europe, which you do not touch.  In
Russia, for example, there is
nowhere to get the same gasoline.  Russia was both an
importer and an exporter of gasoline.
Who has it now?  It won't take it from Latvia, Lithuania, or Estonia
.  Yes, a little bit is coming from Belarus
now.  It won't take it from Kazakhstan.
Kazakhstan has restricted the sale of
your gasoline abroad.  Yes.   Yes.
In this regard,
she gave to Tajikistan and Kyrgyzstan, and she gave
everything to Mongolia.
India.
Look, from India, yes, you physically cannot transport gasoline in the
quantities that the Russian Federation needs
from India.
This is because you have control
over the sea there.  You're telling me now:
No, physically, look, you physically do
n't have the fleet to transport such
volumes of gasoline.
Well, look, let's say that gasoline, yes,
let's say it didn't come in the form of oil, right?
Well, some part went in the form of
oil, yes, not unrefined crude oil
, yes, to one country or another
where it was refined,
some part went already in processed
form, in the form of gasoline.  Now Russia is
losing money on gasoline exports and
is leaving this processing within the country,
feeding itself with foreign imports.
That's right, look, no, look, there is
no external gasoline.  And Ukraine continues, yes, to
attack oil refineries.
The thing is, it's a cumulative
effect, right?  It's not like, look, an
oil refinery can't
be built in a week, right?  Just like, for
example,
you can't build a marketplace warehouse in a week.  True,
don't inflate, don't use two fingers.   The
Wilbury warehouse burns down completely
.  If you have a strike from one or two
drones there at one or another
oil refinery.  I watched
an interview with a guy who
worked in an oil refinery his whole life and was a
technician.  On average, such a plant
takes 2 weeks to restore.  If
he hits the second time, it will take a little
longer.  If there is a third, fourth, fifth,
sixth strike, then, yes, a long
restoration of this or that oil refinery is underway.
But
just look, they don’t just hit
somewhere; they hit in the refinery there is a central
AVT unit, yes, and a
primary processing unit.  They hit it, but
it can’t be restored so easily.
Look, why did some factories, after the
strikes, write that restoration
would take place in 2027?  Yes,
I heard that, yes, I heard that story
there and so on.  This is another
corruption scheme; in short, these are the
people who want to make money there and
launder money.  I see what is happening in Moscow
.  I arrived at Lukoil the day before yesterday
, yes, let's say Rosneft always
gave 50 liters without any problems.  Lukoil always has a
20 liter limit.  I stop
at Lukoil,
get out, and he's like, "What's the full story?"  I was
like, "I'm taken aback."  I say: "What do you mean until it's
full? Well, that's it, there's gas left."  He says:
“They’ve now brought us everything we need,
in short, maybe there are no restrictions.”
This is Lukon.
Look, look again.  This means that Moscow,
yes, Moscow will
always be pulled out at the expense of the regions.  It was the same in the
Soviet Union, right?  In the regions there was no
sausage, damn it, no butter.
Moscow had everything.  It has always been in Moscow.
Moscow will be there until the very end, so they
will continue to draw gasoline from the regions into Moscow,
and so on.  Yes, that's a fact.
That's understandable.  But look, I
also visit the regions.  Let's say I
take my wife to visit her parents in the
Vladimir region twice a month.  That is, for everything,
even the peak of the crisis.  That is, I am driving on a
towpath.
Wait, is she from a village in the
Vladimir region?
Well, you could say from the village.  And what?
Understood.  No, I thought she was from Moscow
too.
No, my first wife was a Muscovite.
Well, I'll tell you this, in short.
Here I am, riding on a plaid.  I drive on a toll road,
which means I always have gas on my toll road
.  Yes, entering there already, yes,
scarves, there in the city where she lives,
I will not name.  There are two
gas stations there.  There's one gas station - privately owned,
where you can buy 95 at any time
, but for 100 rubles.
Yes, for 100.
Either Oil, they don't have Rosneft there, they have
IL there, or Oilil, which, yes, it
will be 70 rubles there, in short, the fifth one will cost
63, uh, ninety-second, but you'll have to
stand in line for 30-40 minutes.
Well, yeah, that's brutal.  Well, 30-40 minutes is
not 2-3 days, it’s not an hour, not two, not three.
Well, yes, 40 minutes is not an hour.
It's 2/3 hours.
That's all, you see, what an educated
young man he is.  Everything is correct.
Yes, that's it, you see,
that's why 40 minutes of discomfort in this
region and 0 minutes in Moscow when you're
standing.  But this is a small difference.  Yes,
no, I don't argue.  There are regions where
traffic jams last for 2 days.  There are such regions in Russia
.
I'm not going to shout at you now that
everything is always the same in Russia, in short, and
we have gasoline everywhere.  There are
logistical problems in certain
regions, unfortunately.  And I think that,
well, sooner or later they
will be resolved anyway, because I see the developments for
protecting oil refineries, protecting power plants,
and so on, which
will now be implemented against drones.
Well, it is impossible to fight without creating
some new, innovative, so
to speak, solutions for protecting certain
objects.  In any case, war is the
engine of progress, no matter how scary it may
sound, yes, in certain
situations.  Therefore, in any case, I
believe that in a year or two, the
same NTZ will no longer be so easily
damaged by a drone.  Only
ballistics.  Only ballistics.
Unfortunately, you have problems with ballistics
.
Well, keep trying for now, yes.  But for now, Shtilerman
says that already...
Well, the only thing that bothered me
was your latest appointment, yes,
your
drop-off.   Yes.
This guy is interesting.   A
serious man.  Serious.  Serious.
What do you know about him?
This is not cheese.  Well, this is the first one, the one
on the armored personnel carrier back then.
Is that why you know him?  Understood.  Yes.
Well, I know that he went from being a
sergeant, roughly speaking, to being a general.  That
is, he went through this entire
chain there and so on.  Well, I was
n't really interested in him, yes, but
I watched some videos about him
.  That is, I understand that this
person, this person is dangerous.
This man is dangerous.  This is not
Syrsky, who organized meat
storms there and did something to the heads there.
This man is now dangerous,
he stood naked.
Cunning.   This is a
problem for Russia
now.
This is the general.
Understood.
Therefore, we must act like Israel.
Rocket into the apartment.
Yes,
but unfortunately it doesn't allow it.
What does not allow it?
I don't know why he doesn't destroy our top
brass.  It doesn't work at all.
In general, in
general.
Well, it doesn't work.  No, they don’t work on
your generals, on your, uh, one or
another of the first ones.
And ours are working.
Well, yes, a couple of generals were killed.
Not a couple, a lot.
Oh,
what do you think, about Stoner's Kyiv,
in short, is this a Russian fabrication?
I don't know whose idea this was.  Either
Russian, or our SBU guys
specifically told him off like that, you know, because
he was, in short, a vatnik there,
in short, yes, but everyone laughs at them.  Why should you
pick him up if he was a horseman, and
then, when the war started, he seemed to have
turned against Russia and left?
No, he seems to be, in short, well, in general,
he’s somehow incomprehensible, like, I don’t know what kind of
joke this is with
Well, it’s a joke, of course.  When I
heard, well yes, Kstur Web 2, this is,
of course, serious.
OK.  Do you have any other questions?   Not yet
, I'll run on.   Okay,
let's see you.  Vaisya.  Well
[laughter]
they're all kind of tipsy now, are
n't they?  Like, subscribe.  Komen.  Subscribe
to our WhatsApp channel.  Here is the QR code.  There,
news similar to that
in the Telegram channel is posted for those who don’t have
Telegram or who don’t use it for
other reasons.  Subscribe to our
WhatsApp channel.